more than 5 years after it launched
bullan futures for trading the National
Stock Exchange in January 2024 surpass
Farm derivatives exchange ncdex to
become India's second largest commodity
derivatives platform the number one MCX
is still a fair bit ahead of both NSE
the country's biggest Stock Exchange by
traded volume and value clocked
commodity derivates volumes volumes of
38,000 418 rupees today's next news is
promoter ICICI Bank has acquired an
additional 1.4% stake in ICI Lombard
General Insurance company threw the Open
Market on Tuesday for
1,164 CR rupees the lender bought
6,982 1852 shares through multiple block
deals on the stock exchanges at ours
1,6 66.3 5 a share as of December end
the private sector lender held a
47.91 per stake in the insurance major
today's next news is Mahindra and
Mahindra limited revealed on February
27th the tar Earth Edition a distinctive
variant inspired by the tar desert a
statement from M andm said the tar Earth
Edition seeks to expand upon the
adventurous Heritage of the Mahindra her
by enchanting and growing the community
of tar
enthusiasts the company said that
crafted with a distinctive Saturn mat
desert Fury finish today's next news is
Reserve Bank of India on February 27th
asked Bank boards and Senior Management
to exercise caution on risk data
aggregation and reporting practices
besides ensuring adequate resources for
execution in its Master Direction on the
filing of supervisory returns released
on February
27th the central bank said the
validation of risk data aggregation and
risk reporting practices needs to be
conducted today's next news is Vodafone
idea board approved the plan to raise up
to 45,000 CR rupees through equity and
debt said the company in an exchange
filing on February 27th the company will
raise 20,000 CR rupees through a
combination of equity or Equity linked
instruments
and the rest wire debt Vodafone idea
will continue to be engaged with its
lenders for tying up the debt funding
after pay Equity Fund raise today's next
news is UAE based 66-year-old Indian
businessman fos Merchant has donated 1
million dhams to ensure the release of
900 prisoners from the Gulf Nation Under
the eus of the Forgotten Society
initiative founded in
2008 he has helped help in the release
of over 20,000 prisoners by paying their
debts and donating money to help them
fly back home today's next news is
India's adani green energy is looking to
raise $49 million via US dollar
denominated bonds with a doorto door
tenor of 18 years the company said in a
regulatory filing on Tuesday Reuters had
earlier reported that hadani green
energy was looking to raise around $500
million by issuing dollar Bonds in March
today's next news is Reserve Bank of
India has granted a payment aggregator
license to Amazon pay with this Amazon
pay joins the list of the elite group of
companies authorized to offer online
Merchant payment services we are excited
and thankful to receive the final
authorization from The Reserve Bank of
India to function as a payment
aggregator Amazon spokesperson said
today's next news is enforcement
directorate has filed a supplementary
complaint against four accused in Pay
6,600 rupees Crow Bitcoin scam according
to enforcement directorate the accused
collected Bitcoins from public in 2017
with false promise of 10% monthly return
subsequent searches conducted at the
accused's premises found multiple luxury
cars including a Mercedes and an Audi
today's next news is sjvn limited
through its wholly owned subsidary sjvn
green energy limited has signed a power
usage agreement with Jammu and Kashmir
power Corporation limited to supply 300
megawatt of solar power from its 1,000
megawatt banir solar power project in
Rajasthan the power generated from the
project will be used by government
entities either directly or through this
SCS